You're awake.
I'm sorry.
Why the sudden apology?
Our blind date was fake.
It was all set up.
They told me to get close to you
and investigate you.
So what did you find out?
Aren't you mad?
No, I'm not.
If it weren't for them,
I wouldn't have met you.
But I suspect they made a mistake.
They should be investigating Pei Ning.
I have one more thing to confess.
I stole your latest
big data analysis algorithm.
You gave them my algorithm.
If they are using my algorithm,
I can detect it here
and find their IP address.
I suspect it now.
This IP matches the one
from the big data analysis experiment post.
Pei Song.
Exactly.
So,
they've been using me all along.
Mom?
Shiya.
Song Shiya!
Your brother committed suicide.
My son!
Shiya.
Uncle, Auntie.
It's you.
If it weren't for you,
Auntie.
why would my son get addicted to gambling?
And how could he owe so much debt?
Mom, calm down.
This has nothing to do with Pei Song.
How could it have nothing to do with him?
Auntie, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I failed to protect Shiya's brother.
You can beat me or scold me.
But the most urgent thing right now
is for you two to move in with us.
My poor son!
So,
you're saying
history is repeating itself?
In the previous life,
your brother also owed gambling debts
and participated in the big data experiment analysis.
Later,
something happened to your parents too.
Until you found out
that all of this was related to Pei Ning.
To get close to Pei Ning,
you divorced me
and married him.
Then...
Then what?
Every time, you died.
At a different time,
in a different place,
but the ending never changed.
So,
when you said you wanted my parents to move in,
it was to protect them?
You're up.
Let's eat.
Where's Dad?
He went out for a walk.
A walk?
Didn't we tell him to stay home and not wander off?
Get some clothes.
Be careful.
Murderer.
Mom.
Give me back my son.
You are all murderers.
Son,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's fine.
Let's go.
We'll only provoke her by staying here.
Mom is here.
Don't worry.
The nurses will take good care of Mom.
I've also made it clear to the doctors.
You can come see Mom in a few days,
okay?
Okay.
Relax.
It's fine.
Everything will be okay.
Son.
In our past life,
your brother also owed gambling debts,
and participated in the big data experiment analysis.
Later,
something happened to your parents.
Until you found out
that it was all related to Pei Ning.
To get close to Pei Ning,
you divorced me
and married him.
He is my...
classmate.
Why haven't I
ever heard you mention him before?
How did you meet Pei Song?
Introduced by the elders.
Grandpa.
Have you figured it out?
I'll drink for her, alright?
It seems
your love for Song Shiya
is true love.
My brother can't drink.
I'll drink for him.
That day I saw
Ningning developed an AI
exactly like Shiya.
Every time you die.
Different times,
different places,
but the ending never changes.
Xiaoning used to have a crush on Shiya.
Then why do you still want to marry Shiya?
Because I love her.
You love her?
Did you know her before?
I've known her for a long time.
If it's really like what Pei Song said,
I'd rather face it alone.
This matter has nothing to do with Pei Song.
He shouldn't have to bear so much.
Can destiny
really not be changed?
What exactly must I do
to protect Shiya?
Shiya,
are you hungry?
Do you want to get up and eat something?
You haven't eaten all day.
Let me cook a bowl of noodles for you.
Shiya.